Midari, I don't recommend
pulling the trigger on that gun.
（夢子(ゆめこ)）生志摩(いきしま)さん
その銃の引き金を引くのは
お勧めしません
You're begging for your life?
Man, how boring!
（妄(みだり)）あ？ 今更 命乞いか？
つまんねえことすんじゃ…
That's my gun. Look at the barrel.
それは私の銃です
銃口を見てください
赤い印が付いていますでしょう？
It has a red mark, right?
銃身に たっぷりと
口紅を詰めさせていただきました
I filled the barrel with lipstick.
はあ？
私は弾を３発込めました
I put three bullets in.
つまり６発中３発
In other words, there's a three
in six chance the gun will misfire.
暴発の可能性があるということ
２分の１です
That's 50 percent,
and you're taking all the risk.
それも あなたが
一方的にリスクを負う…
（カチッ）
ヘヘッ 外れかよ
No luck, huh?
ウソですよ
That was a lie.
I didn't put a single bullet in.
本当は１発も込めていません
What? Seriously?
はあ？ マジかよ！
チッ… ったく！
Jeez.
ちなみに
口紅程度の物が詰まっていても
By the way, it seems that lipstick
isn't enough to cause a gun to misfire.
銃は問題なく発射されるようです
I don't care.
Let's go on to the next round.
どうでもいい
さあ 次 いこうぜ
生志摩さん あなたはどうして
Midari, why did you ask me
to play this game?
こんなギャンブルを
持ちかけて こられたのですか？
（妄）はあ？
んなもん決まってる！
スリルだ！
Why else? For the thrill of it!
命を懸けたスリルが
快感だからだよ
The thrill of risking your life
is pure joy!
I want to go numb to a thrill
you could never get in real life!
尋常じゃ味わえないスリルに
シビれてえんだよ〜！
ダメなんだよ
Money's not good enough.
It doesn't make me feel anything.
金なんかじゃ
あたしは みじんも感じねえ
いくら稼ごうが失おうが
どうだっていい
No matter how much I make or lose,
it doesn't matter. It doesn't matter...
どうだっていいんだ
ウヘッ
あたしの左目は 全く視力がない
I can't see out of my left eye at all.
Why do you think that is?
なぜだと思う？
The president took it as the prize
for a gambling match!
会長に
取られたんだよ！
ギャンブルの
支払いとして！
アハハ ハハハハ…
〜
（妄）
子供のころから 違和感があった
Something always felt off
since I was little.
勝利や称賛 畏怖も
Winning, praise, the fear of others,
even when I made a fortune at the academy.
学園で大金を稼いだときだって
None of it really made me happy.
何ひとつ あたしを心から
喜ばせたものはなかった
（綺羅莉(きらり)）さて…
（妄）はっ
Now, you owe 300 million yen.
（綺羅莉）
あなたの負け分３億円だけれど
- Do you have a way to pay it?
- Of course not!
支払いの当ては あるのかしら？
は？ あるわけねえだろ
そんなもん！
Gambling's so damn boring.
やっぱ ギャンブルなんて
クソつまんねえな〜
借金なんざ いくらあっても
痛くもかゆくもねえしよ
Debt doesn't mean a goddamn thing to me.
なるほど その恐れ知らずが
あなたのギャンブルの強さなのね
I see. That lack of fear
is what makes you good at gambling.
あなたのような人には
お金というより
I'd prefer people like you
pay with your lives, not money.
その人生で支払ってもらいたい
ところだけれど…
But you're not the type men really like.
あなたは あまり
男好きするタイプではないわね
人生計画には向いてないかしら
You may not be appropriate
for a life plan.
あっ そうだ
I know...
あ？
（綺羅莉）裏側…
The other side. Have you ever seen
the other side of the moon?
月の裏側って見たことある？
（妄）は？
（綺羅莉）もちろん ないわよね
Of course you haven't.
Perhaps you've seen a picture of it.
But I've never seen it for myself.
画像ならあるけれど
私がこの目で見たことはない
みんなで私をだましているだけで
Everyone's just lying to me.
Maybe there's an alien base there.
もしかしたら
本当に宇宙人の基地があるのかも
You can't totally deny
that ridiculous idea, can you?
なんてバカな妄想も
完全には否定できない
は… 何の話？
What are you--?
考えてみれば 私…
I just realized that I've never seen
the back of someone's eye socket.
眼球の裏側って見たことがない
（妄）あ… うっ は…
I'll buy your left eye
for 300 million yen.
あなたの左目を
３億で買うわ
目の裏側は
どんな色をしているの？
What color is the back of an eye?
神経は どこでどんなふうに
つながっているの？
Where are the nerves? How do they connect?
How does it smell? Is there blood?
匂いは？ 血は出るの？
I want to know, not from reading it
in a book, but from seeing it myself.
知りたいのよ
知識ではなく 経験として
She doesn't see me as human.
（妄）
こいつ…
あたしを人間として見ていない
摘出手術は あしたにしましょう
We can do the removal operation tomorrow.
You have class. We can do it after school.
授業もあることだし
放課後でいいわ
（妄）ウヘヘ ハハハハ
てめえ イカレてるよ！
You're insane! You're a pervert!
（妄）この ド変態が！
（清華(さやか)）会長！
President!
（妄）ヘヘッ
（グサッ）
（るな）ふえ〜 やるねえ
Impressive.
（清華）あっ…
うっ ぐ… うう…
ぐ…
（綺羅莉）ふ〜ん
（妄）ぐっ…
I see. Yes, I've never seen anyone
tear their own eye out.
なるほど… 確かに
自分で自分の目をえぐる様子は
見たことがなかったわ
ふ〜ん
It wasn't that interesting.
Thanks. You can go.
大して面白いものでは
なかったわね
お疲れさま 帰っていいわ
（妄）
ウヘヘ ウヘ ハッ ハッ
ハハハ ハ〜
て… てめえ あたしは
目… 目… 目をえぐったんだぞ
That's not fair!
I... stabbed out my eye!
ウヘヘヘ お前が言ったことだろ！
This was your idea, right?
Take more pleasure in it!
もっと喜べよ！
I told you, I'm satisfied. Thanks.
ええ だから満足してるわよ
ご苦労さま
ウヘッ
よ〜く分かったぜ
I finally understand...
Pain... This pain is true gambling!
痛み…
この痛みこそが
本当のギャンブル！
President, one more time!
Let's gamble once more!
会長 もう１回だ！
もう１回
ギャンブルしようぜ
もう金は ないんでしょう？
You're out of money, right?
I've seen what I had to see.
見るべきものは 見せてもらったし
- There's no point to gamble with you.
- I've got another eye, right?
やる義理もなければ 意味もないわ
（妄）
目(め)ん玉(たま)は もう１個あんだろ？
３億賭けて
もう１回 ギャンブルだ！
Let's gamble once more
for 300 million yen.
妄 あなた 生徒会に入りなさい
Midari, join the student council.
Not interested! I just want to gamble--
興味ねえよ！
んなことより
ギャンブルを…
If you do...
生徒会に入れば
いずれ殺してあげるわ
someday, I'll kill you.
（妄）最高だった
It was the greatest experience of my life.
My brain went numb.
頭の奥がシビれたぜ
I finally understood why
the whole world loves to gamble.
世の中の人間が
ギャンブルする理由が
ようやく分かった
痛いのは嫌だ
I don't want the pain. I don't want
to die. That's what makes it great!
死ぬのは怖い
だからこそ いいんだよ
なあ 夢子
お前も そうなんだろ？
You're the same, right, Yumeko?
さて どうでしょうか？
I couldn't say.
（妄）ウヘッ
今更
カマトトぶってんじゃねえよ
Don't even try to hide it.
言ったろ？
I told you that we're the same.
That's how I know.
あたしとお前は
同類だから分かるんだ
The president's the greatest,
but she refuses to do it with me.
会長は最高の女だが
いつまでたっても してくれねえ
So, I'm counting on you, Yumeko.
期待してるぜ 夢子〜
（部下Ａ）２セット目 開始だよ
It's time for round two.
（鈴井(すずい)）
どう並べるか…
How do I line these up? Unlike
the first round, where there was no hint,
全くヒントのなかった
１セット目と違い
今度は 僕と夢子が
確実に共有している情報がある
this time there's information
that Yumeko and I definitely share.
The way all three of us lined our cards up
in round one Me, Ikishima, Yumeko.
１セット目
僕ら３人のカードの並びだ
僕か 生志摩か 夢子か
そのうちのどれかを
再現するべきだ
I should match one of our hands.
僕の頭では
Yumeko would know
that my brain is only capable
この３択しか思いつかないことを
夢子なら分かってくれてる
of coming up with those three options.
But the problem is...
ただ 問題は…
I only remember how my cards
and Yumeko's were lined up
僕が覚えてるのは
注目してた自分と夢子の
カードの並びだけってことだ
since that's all I was looking at.
待てよ
Wait. Isn't it normal
not to remember them all?
全部 覚えてないなんて
普通じゃないか？
とっさに５枚のカードの並びを
３セットも覚えられるものじゃない
Normally, you couldn't remember
the order of three sets of five cards.
If Ikishima remembers something,
生志摩が覚えているなら
夢子のカードより
she'd be more likely to remember
my cards instead of Yumeko's.
基準となる僕のカード
なんじゃないか？
But that's not true for Yumeko.
でも 夢子は違う
I can say for sure that Yumeko
remembers all the hands.
夢子なら間違いなく
全部のカードを覚えてる
決めた
That's it! I'll copy Yumeko's hand
from round one.
１セット目の
夢子の並びを再現する！
I'll only say this once more.
（綺羅莉）もう一度だけ言うわ
芽亜里(めあり) 生徒会に入りなさい
Mary, join the student council.
（芽亜里）
１点だけ伺っても
よろしいですか？
May I ask one question?
（綺羅莉）何かしら？
What is it? I'll be happy
to answer any questions.
何でも聞いてちょうだい
う…
家畜制度についてです
It's about the house pet system.
人間を家畜にする
The way you turn humans into house pets
is terrible. Why do you go that far?
あまりにもひどい
なぜ ここまでする必要が
あるんですか？
ん…
Pretty, isn't it?
（綺羅莉）きれいでしょ？
でも こんなにかわいい魚たちも
But even these cute fish live in a world
where it's survival of the fittest.
弱肉強食なのよ
もしも
最下層の魚だけ集めてきたら
If you gathered the fish at the bottom
of the food chain, what would happen?
どうなると思う？
A new bottom would form.
やっぱり その中でも
最下層の魚は生まれるのよ
そして時には
And sometimes, the weak fish
would steal food from the strong.
弱い魚が強い魚の餌を
奪うこともある
So, what if these were humans?
じゃあ もし これが人間だったら？
I want to see for myself.
I'm very curious.
見てみたいのよ
とっても興味深いわ
はあ？
The odds this game will end in a tie
are 100 percent.
（夢子）予告しましょう
このギャンブルは100パーセント
引き分けで終わらせます
Hey! What are you talking about?
（妄）
おい おい おい おい
何 言ってんだよ
The risk of gambling
is the greatest pleasure!
ギャンブルのリスクが 最高の快楽
あたしとお前は
その点で同類だろ？
You and I are the same that way, right?
You want to risk death with me, right?
殺し合いを望んでんだろ？
Risk death, huh?
殺し合い… ね
やはり３セットに
限らせていただいてよかったです
I was right to limit it to three games.
You're lying! You want to feel
the risk of death if you lose, right?
うそだろ？
負けたら死ぬ
そのリスクを
全力で感じたいんだろ？
No. I'm not feeling
any fear at all right now.
いいえ
今は恐怖なんて
これっぽっちもありません
だって 私は
鈴井さんを信じていますから
Because I believe in Ryota.
（妄）チッ あたしは６発込める
I'm putting in six bullets!
If you think you can get a draw, then try!
引き分け狙い
やれるもんならやってみろ！
遠慮なく
As you wish.
I hope Yumeko sees what I'm trying to do.
Please... I'm begging you!
（鈴井）
夢子が 僕の思考に
気付いてくれれば きっと…
頼む！
You're ready, right?
（妄）準備は いいな？
オープンだ
Show your cards.
あっ！ や… やった！
Five to three. Yumeko wins!
５対３ 夢子の勝ち！
ハハ… ハア〜
She got all five right?
（妄）
５枚 全当てだと!?
サインもなしに
Without any sign...
How could she do that?
なんで そんなことが
できるんだよ？
偶然なわきゃねえ
It can't be a coincidence.
Trying to get them right means
taking the risk of getting them wrong.
全当て狙いは
全外しのリスクと隣り合わせ
She took the risk to get results.
リスクを冒して
結果を取りにいったんだ
ウヘッ 夢子
Yumeko.
あっ！
やっぱり お前は
あたしの見込みどおりの女だ
You really were just who I hoped you were.
生志摩さん
Midari, are you ready?
心の準備は よろしいですか？
ウヘッ いいぞ よ〜く狙え！
I sure am! Aim carefully!
One in two...
（妄）
２分の１だ
There's a one in two chance
the bullet comes out.
２分の１の確率で弾が出る！
あんなものとは比べ物にならない
It's way better than that was.
ヒッ ヒ…
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
ヒッ ヒッ ヒッ ヒッ…
し… し… し…
I'm gonna die!
死ぬ〜！ あっ！
ハア ハア ハア ハア…
ハア… ハア〜
は… 外れか
No luck?
Nope. This is my gun. The second chamber
doesn't contain a bullet either.
（夢子）そうですね これは私の銃
２発目も弾は入っていません
ヘッ 淡々と引きやがって
You're so cold.
You're not scared to fire? You sadist!
撃っちまう恐怖は ねえのかよ？
このサド野郎が！
I'm not. I knew this was my gun.
ええ
だって こちらが私の銃だって
分かってましたもの
（妄）はあ？
（夢子）弾の重さがあるでしょう？
The bullets weigh something, right?
There's a difference of six bullets.
６発分の差です
This gun doesn't even weigh
a kilogram, right?
この拳銃は
１キロもないですよね？
一方 弾は恐らく15グラムはある
But the bullets probably weigh
15 grams apiece.
That's a ten percent difference.
10分の１もの差です
さすがに分かりますよ
I can tell that.
（妄）
フヘッ そうだよな
さすがに分かる
That's right. You can tell.
んなわけ ねえだろ！
Of course you can't!
What's the deal with your senses?
どんな感覚してんだよ！
でも 分かりましたよ
But I was able to tell.
（妄）
フッ 人間業じゃねえ
That's inhuman.
At this rate, I'm going to lose for sure.
このままじゃ
確実に あたしの負け
Yumeko really is amazing.
She read my mind perfectly.
（鈴井）
やっぱり夢子は すごい
僕の考えを完璧に読んでくれた
Yes. Understood.
（部下Ａ）
はい はい 了解しました
鈴井 ３セット目いくよ
Ryota, time for game three.
（鈴井）
次も当然 再現 全当てできる！
I can help her get all of it again.
あっ な… 何だ これ!?
What is this? That's cheating!
イカサマじゃないか！
な… 何なんだよ これ
What is this?
イカサマだ！ イカサマ！
That's cheating! Cheating!
Right. Just line up the cards.
はい はい　いいから並べてよ
（鈴井）ふざけるな！
Shut up! She could get killed! You can't--
命が懸かっているんだぞ！
こんな状態で…
（妄）
鈴井！
Ryota! Line up the goddamn cards!
さっさと並べろ！
あと10秒で並べなきゃ
夢子をぶっ殺す！
If you can't do it in ten seconds,
I'll kill Yumeko! Ten, nine...
10… ９…
- No way! If she does that, Yumeko will...
- ...eight, seven, six, five...
（鈴井）
ウソだろ
こんなことされたら
夢子は… くっ…
I have to line them up.
It's no good. I can't think of anything.
並べなきゃ
ダメだ
何も思いつかない
思いつかないなら…
And if I can't...
Okay.
よし フフッ 夢子
Yumeko.
（夢子）生志摩さん
Midari, that isn't very nice
of you at all.
随分と つまらないことを
してくれましたね
お仕置きです
This is your punishment.
I put two bullets in.
私は弾を２発込めました
（妄）
アハハハハ アッ ハハハ〜
お前さ 最高だ！
You're the best!
I had the wrong idea. I thought you were
like me, that you rejoice in risk-taking.
勘違いしてたぜ
お前はリスクを喜ぶ
あたしと同類だって
違う！ お前は搾取する側
But I was wrong! You're a thinker.
The same type as the president!
会長と同じ人種だ！
If you're putting in two bullets, so am I.
お前が２発なら あたしも２発だ
No. How can she do that
in this circumstance?
（鈴井）
そんな… なんで この状況で…
You're ready, right, Yumeko?
Reveal the cards.
夢子 覚悟はいいな？
オープンだ
つまらない
How boring.
（妄）あ？
（夢子）ご存じでしたか？
Did you know that Ryota is right-handed?
鈴井さんは右利きなんです
なのに 今日は
１ ２セット目にかぎって
But for the first two games,
he used his left hand to flip the cards.
左手でカードを
並べてらっしゃった
加えて言えば その際
波線のカードの向きが逆でした
In addition to that,
the wave card was backwards.
となると…
Which means one thing.
考えられることは ひとつでしょう
私たちが見ていた映像は
The video we saw was reflected in
a mirror. Left and right were backwards.
左右が鏡映しに
反転されたものだった
一方 現在 ３セット目は右手です
But now, he's using his right hand.
ということは
今回にかぎり反転はない
In other words,
this time there's no reflection.
でも それだけでは ２セット目で
But that doesn't explain
how Ryota was able to recreate
鈴井さんが私の並べ方を
再現できたのがおかしい
the way I lined up my cards
in the second game.
He should've lined it up backwards.
But that wasn't what happened.
並びが 逆になるはずですから
でも そうじゃなかった
ということは
Which means our image
was reversed as well.
私たちの姿もまた 反転されていた
お互いが鏡映しの映像を
見ていたんです
We were both looking at reversed images.
There's no way you could trick someone
with such a stupid cheat.
こんなくだらないイカサマで
人を欺けるはずもない
Please don't insult me, okay?
バカにするのも
大概にしてくださいね
鈴井さんの手は
完全に予想どおりです
Ryota's actions
were just what I predicted.
（妄）
このイカサマも織り込み済み
She took this cheating into account
完璧に勝ち筋を立ててたわけか
and perfectly incorporated it
into her plan.
やっぱり あたしじゃ
かなわなかったよ
I knew I couldn't beat her.
夢子 おめでとう
Yumeko, congratulations.
ヘッ
お前の負けだ
You lose.
えっ
なんで…
How?
She got them all wrong!
全外し!?
I can't believe it!
（妄）まさかだ！
まさか お前みたいな女が
現れてくれるなんて！
I can't believe a girl like you
appeared before me!
アハッ もう我慢できねえ
I can't take it anymore.
It's your turn. Show your cards, Yumeko!
お前の番だ 開けよ 夢子！
ずっと探してた
I've been looking so long...
for the greatest woman imaginable,
あたしにとって最高の女
one like the president.
会長のような人間を！
あたしを支配してくれ！
Control me! Please!
お前が連れてる あの男のように！
Like the boy you keep with you.
Let me join you.
なあ あたしも混ぜてくれよ！
お前みたいな女に
ヤラれたかったんだ
I wanted a girl like you to kill me.
I'll entrust you with everything.
全部 お前に託すからさ！
Rule over everything I have!
あたしの全てを支配してくれよ！
Show your hand and let me die!
早く！ カードを開いて
あたしをイカせてくれ〜！
お前だ！
お前じゃないとダメなんだ！
You, it has to be you!
それ以外は ただのオナニー
Anything else is just masturbation.
お前じゃなきゃ
あの日の喜びは味わえない！
You're the only way I can feel
the joy I felt on that day. Do it!
さあ！ ゆ め…
（夢子）
とことん 予想どおりでしたね
This is just what I expected.
あなたが負けようとしていたことは
すぐに分かりました
I knew instantly
that you were trying to lose.
なぜ 鈴井さんを
ディーラーにすることを
Why'd you agree
to let Ryota be the dealer?
承諾したのですか？
You didn't have any guarantee
that we didn't have a sign.
私たちにサインがないという
確信もないのに
（妄）えっ いや 待ってくれ！
No, wait...
The only reason you pulled the trigger
without hesitation during the first game
１セット目
ためらいなく引き金を引いたのも
あなたは自分の危険を
顧みなかったにすぎない
was that you didn't care
if you were in danger.
まあ ここまでは
いいとしましょう
Well, that's fine, though.
But this is just terrible.
しかし これは あまりにひどい
待て おい！
それ以上 めくるな！
Wait! Hey, don't flip over another card.
This particular cheat
was made to be found out.
このイカサマは
気付かれるように作られている
この波線カード
This wave card.
例えば 波が
もうひとつあるカードであれば
What if there was another wave on it?
どうですか？
上下が たまたま
入れ替わっている場合と
You couldn't tell if it just happened
to be upside-down.
区別が つきませんよね？
全てが 到底
You can't have done all this
just to win the game. So, why?
ギャンブルに勝つための行動では
ありえません
では なぜ？
Victory to you is being killed.
あなたにとっての勝ちとは…
殺されること
それが
あなたの勝利条件
That is your victory condition.
夢子も全外し！
３セット目も引き分けだ！
Yumeko got everything wrong too!
It's a draw again!
（妄）お… おかしい
This doesn't make sense. It doesn't
make any sense. It just doesn't.
筋が通ってない
矛盾してるじゃねえか
なぜ２発 弾を込めた？
Why put two bullets in? You could've
put in zero since you knew you'd win.
ゼロにして
カード当てで勝てばいい
２発込めた上で全外しなんて
撃たれるリスクを上げるだけ
Putting in two
and then getting them all wrong
just increases the risk you'll get shot.
It's simple.
There are six chambers in the gun.
簡単な話ですよ
銃の装填(そうてん)数は６発
私が２発込めたことで
空の弾倉は４発になった
After I put in two bullets,
there were four chambers left.
If the score difference was five,
one bullet would definitely be fired.
ということは５点差なら
絶対に発射されることに
なりますよね？
If you get all five cards wrong,
a tie's impossible.
であれば ５枚外せば
絶対に引き分けはない
I knew that that's what you'd think.
そうあなたが考えると
思ったんですよ
気まぐれで
１枚や２枚当てられては
If you decided to get one or two right,
I might get shot.
私が撃たれる
可能性があった
こんなものは ギャンブルではない
This isn't gambling.
価値も興味も
何ひとつ見いだせない
It's just a stupid game, pointless,
and not even entertaining!
くだらないお遊戯！
先ほど 私とあなたは
同類ではないとおっしゃいましたね
You just said
that you and I weren't alike, right?
同感ですよ
I agree.
Gambling is fun because both sides
have the chance to feel pain.
ギャンブルは
両者が痛みを感じるから楽しいもの
Why are you trying to monopolize
all the pain for yourself?
なぜ あなただけが
痛みを独占しようと
しているのですか？
あなたはギャンブルを
楽しんでいるのではない
You're not enjoying the gambling.
You just want to die!
ただの死にたがり！
私が いちばん
大嫌いなタイプの人間です
You're the type I hate most.
端的に申し上げて
In short...
ムカつくんですよ あなた！
you piss me off!
（妄）
何なんだよ それ…
What is she saying?
こいつは
自分が死ぬリスクを負ってまで
She risked death
to force the game to a tie.
引き分けを狙ったんだ
イカレてやがる
She's insane. She's far beyond
what I imagined, what I dreamed!
あたしの想像の埒外(らちがい)
理想を超えた存在！
夢子！
Yumeko!
You're my goddess!
お前は あたしの…
女神様！
- This was a waste of time, huh?
- Yumeko! Wait!
時間のムダでしたね
（妄）
ゆ… 夢子！ ま… 待ってくれ！
頼む！ ゆめっ…
Yume... it has to be you!
お… お前じゃなきゃ
ダメなんだ！
１発でいい！
Just one shot is all I need!
Give me pain, please!
あたしに痛みをくれ〜！
クスッ
THE GIRLS THAT REFUSE
お断りです
I refuse.
今 何て言ったの？
What did you say?
（芽亜里）
聞こえなかったんですか？
Did you not hear me?
生徒会に入るなんて
お断りだって言ったんです！
I said I refuse to join
the student council.
理由を聞かせてもらえる？
May I ask why? You don't like
the way we treat house pets?
家畜に対する態度が
許せなかった？
あなたは そんなに
正義感の強い人だったかしら？
You have a strong sense of justice?
（芽亜里）ぐっ
答える義理はありませんね
I don't have to answer that.
Goodbye.
さようなら
Is Yumeko upset?
（鈴井）
夢子… 何か 機嫌悪い？
（夢子）鈴井さん
（鈴井）はい
- Ryota?
- Yes?
（夢子）
スイーツバイキングに
行きませんか？
Want to go to a sweets buffet?
The coin flip determines who pays.
どちらがおごるかは
コインしだいで！
裏なら私
Tails, it's me.
表なら鈴井さんということで
どうでしょう？
Heads, it's you. How about it?
（鈴井）
えっ いや… 今月 結構厳しくて
No, things are pretty tight this month.
（夢子）お願いできませんか？
Are you absolutely sure?
ああ…
う… 分かった！
Fine, I'm a man. I'll do it.
俺も男だ やるよ！
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
では！
Here we go.
（鈴井）
う〜 頼む　裏 裏 裏 裏…
Please. Tails.
（夢子）
ひとつ お伺いしても
よろしいですか？
May I ask something?
あ？
Why did you keep recreating my hand
先ほどのギャンブル
イカサマに気付いても
なぜ再現を続けられたのですか？
even though you realized
they were cheating?
えっ なんで そんなこと？
Why are you asking?
Please.
お願いします
お答えが頂きたいんです
I want an answer.
う〜ん まあ 時間もなかったし
Well, there was no time.
あんまり考えられなくて…
I couldn't really think.
というか 正直に言うと
And actually...
to be honest...
夢子なら僕がどう対処していいか
分からないってことに
I thought you'd realize
that I didn't know what to do.
気付いてくれる
I hoped you would.
気付いてくれたらいいなって
思ったんだ
はっ！
（鈴井）
ごめん！ あんな命が懸かった場で
I'm sorry. I know that with your life
on the line, I should've thought more.
もっと考えるべきだったとは
思うんだけど
I see. I understand.
なるほど よく分かりました
裏です
鈴井さんの勝ちですね！
It's tails. You win, Ryota.
（鈴井）
は？ おっしゃ！ 助かった！
Yes!
I'm saved!
（夢子）ウフフフ
ありがとうございます
鈴井さん
Thank you, Ryota. Thanks to you,
I had a very fun time gambling.
（鈴井）え？
（夢子）おかげさまで
とっても楽しいギャンブルが
できました
Sense of justice?
（芽亜里）
正義感だと？
It just makes me angrier
how wrong she was.
見当違いなことを言われると
余計に腹が立つ
理由なんて決まってる
There's only one reason.
あいつは家畜を
人間として見ていない
She doesn't see house pets as humans.
She sees them as a lower race.
種(しゅ)として下だと思っている
それは つまり…
In other words...
she insulted me.
私をコケにしてくれたってことだ！
ナメるなよ
And that was a bad idea.
I'll make her regret it.
必ず目に物 見せてやる！
〜
（伊月(いつき)）
お久しぶりです
- It's been forever!
- Thank you!
（ユメミ）
みんな ありがとう！
The school started
to revolve around Yumeko.
（鈴井）
夢子を中心に
学園全体が動き始めている
Of course, you're welcome!
If that happens...
you'll form an idol unit with me.
（ユメミ）
そのときは…
私とアイドルユニットを
組んでもらうわ！
EPISODE 8: THE GIRL WHO DANCES LOVE